Guide to the Robert Blanchon Papers and Collection MSS 220
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Art Production, 144250
  - Subseries A: Artwork, 144259
    - Dr. Farnsworth's Curtains, 1998; 220.2.0025; 151256; 1 item one photograph (Box 17, Object ID: 220.2.0025)
      Dimensions: 20.5" x 34"
      Description: Photograph of the curtains at the Farnsworth House designed by Mies van der Rohe. The curtains were installed following a dispute between the owner and the architect.
    - Gifts for Harold, 1994; 151236 (Box 27, Object ID: 220.2.0006)
      Medium: mixed media
      Dimensions: variable
      Description: Photographs represent gifts received by the character Harold in the play The Boys in the Band (1968) by Matt Crowley. Text panels feature related excerpts from play's script. In the original installation a shelf held a sympathy card. Piece consists of six mounted pages of the script on foam board and four framed images.
    - hap-hazard, 1996; 151252 (Box 29, Object 220.2.0021)
      Medium: c-prints, Plexiglas boxes
      Dimensions: 3" x 2" x 2" each; overall dimensions variable
      Description: Described by Blanchon as 990 Plexiglas boxes filled with "every photo I ever took." 874 Plexiglas boxes present spread across boxes 29-37.
      Each box of contains ~100 Plexiglas boxes.
    - hap-hazard, 1996; 277418 (Box 30, Object 220.2.0021)
    - hap-hazard, 1996; 277419 (Box 31, Object 220.2.0021)
    - hap-hazard, 1996; 277420 (Box 32, Object 220.2.0021)
    - hap-hazard, 1996; 277421 (Box 33, Object 220.2.0021)
    - hap-hazard, 1996; 277422 (Box 34, Object 220.2.0021)
    - hap-hazard, 1996; 277423 (Box 35, Object 220.2.0021)
    - hap-hazard, 1996; 277424 (Box 36, Object 220.2.0021)
    - hap-hazard, 1996; 277425 (Box 37, Object 220.2.0021)
    - Male Call, 1993; 151235 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Medium: ink, paper; ed.unknown, invitation
      Dimensions: 5.5" x 4.5"; schedule: 11" x 8.5"
      Description: Invitation and schedule to fictional conference. Text reads: "You have been cordially invited to attend Male Call, a series of programs for male artists, curators, historians, critics, collectors, and arts administrators -- examining the changing roles of men in society and culture." The archive contains 9 original invitations and one copy of the original schedule.
    - Original Gravestone Rubbings, 1995; 220.2.0011; 151244; 1 item one drawing (Box 46, Object ID: 220.2.0011)
      Medium: graphite on paper
      Dimensions: 36" wide, approx. 60'long
      Description: Original graphite rubbings from uninscribed, commerical gravestones. Used to produce the artwork entitled Untitled (stones).
      Works of art.
    - Razor Burn, 1995; 151246 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Medium: glossy magazine prints
      Description: Honcho magazine issue 18, no. 10 (October 1995): 5-13. Portraits of Blanchon by John Philips of Hound Dog Productions, photographed for a nine-page spread in Honcho magazine.
    - Rock (0-9), 1996; 151249 (Box 22, Object ID: 220.2.0018)
      Medium: gelatin silver prints; ed. possibly three
      Dimensions: 10" x 10" each
      Description: Piece consists of ten prints on foam board.
    - Stem (0-9), 1998; 151255 (Box 52, Object ID: 220.2.0024)
      Medium: toned prints, wood frames; ed. possibly three
      Dimensions: 12" x 9" each
      Description: Piece consists of 10 framed prints.
    - Untitled (1959), 1989; 151231 (Box 38, Object ID: 220.2.0001)
      Medium: c-prints, redwood frames
      Description: Five images of nude boys, photographed from 1950s gay pulp erotica. The original presentation consisted of five framed prints. Only two prints are present in the collection at the Fales Library. Among the three prints not present in the collection, one is known to have been destroyed by water damage.
    - Untitled [I will not get AIDS], 1989; 144557 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Medium: paper sticker
      Dimensions: 9.5" x 7.5"
      Description: Image of former Chicago mayor Richard Daley with the caption "I will not get AIDS." Created as a variation on a series of posters produced by the Chicago Department of Health, Blanchon printed the design on adhesive sheets and, with John Darmour, hung it around the city. The posters' appearance was widely reported in the Chicago press. Collection consists of 68 original stickers.
    - Untitled (sympathy), 1992; 151233 (Box 40, Object ID: 220.2.0003)
      Medium: cibachrome print, wood frame
      Dimensions: 13.25" x 10.75"
      Description: Text read: "We shall always remember with deep gratitude your comforting expression of sympahty."
    - Untitled (sympathy card), 1994; 220.2.0008; 151238; 1 item one photograph (Box 42, Object ID: 220.2.0008)
      Medium: black and white photograph, wood frame
      Dimensions: 31" x 41"
      Description: Text read: "The family of________acknowledges with grateful appreciation your kind expression of sympathy."
      Black-and-white photographs.
    - Untitled (aroma/1981), 1995; 151237 (Box 7, Object ID: 220.2.0007)
      Medium: sepia prints on vellum
      Description: Sepia prints of advertisements from vintage gay magazines. Originally described as including 100 prints. Prints owned by the Fales Library were recreated for the Visual AIDS catalog by Tania Duvergne.
    - Untitled (self-portrait/waste), 1995; 151239 (Box 21, Object ID: 220.2.0009)
      Medium: metal, rubber
      Dimensions: 4.5" diameter, 1.75" deep
      Description: Stainless steel garbage disposal ring inscribed with the manufacturer's name, "WASTE KING."
    - Untitled (stones), 1995; cuid6014; 151240; 1 item one print (Box 43, Object ID: 220.2.0010)
      Medium: diazotype prints on paper
      Dimensions: 36" wide, length variable
      Description: Diazotype "blueprints" of rubbings from uninscribed, commercial gravestones. Prints were intended to fade over time with exposure to light. Piece consists of three rolls of diazotype prints. Each roll is stored separately.
      Scope and Contents
      Object ID: 220.2.0010
    - Untitled (stones), 1995; cuid6015; 277428; 1 item one print (Box 44, Object ID: 220.2.0010)
    - Untitled (stones), 1995; cuid6016; 277429; 1 item one print (Box 45, Object ID: 220.2.0010)
    - Untitled (Death Valley Self-Portrait), 1995; cuid6017; 151242; 1 item one photograph (Box 47, Object ID: 220.2.0012)
      Medium: cibachrome prints, wood frames
      Dimensions: 35.5" x 45.5"
      Description: A self-portrait paired with a landscape photo taken through a car windshield. Piece consists of 2 framed cibachrome prints, stored separately.
      Object ID: 220.2.0012
    - Untitled (Death Valley Self-Portrait), 1995; cuid6018; 277430 (Box 48, Object 220.2.0012)
    - Untitled (gum stain 4), 1995; 220.2.0013; 151243; 1 item one photograph (Box 49, Object ID: 220.2.0013)
      Dimensions: 32.25" x 22.5"
      Description: Originally part of a series of four photographs of gum stained sidewalks. Alternate title: Untitled (9000 Sunset Blvd.), refers to a West Hollywood cruising location where photograph was taken.
    - Untitled (back) -- shirt, 1996; 151247; 1 item one shirt (Box 50, Object ID: 220.2.0016a)
      Medium: clothing labels, thread
      Dimensions: men's medium
      Description: Shirt sewn entirely of clothing labels.
      Textiles.
    - Untitled (back) - mannequin, 1996; 1 item one mannequin (Item 220.2.0016b)
      Mannequins (costume equipment)
    - Untitled (No Corpse…), 1996; 151248 (Box 28, Object ID: 220.2.0017)
      Medium: gelatin silver print
      Dimensions: 16.74" x 23.25"
      Description: Full title: Untitled (No corpse of any person [except those who shall die of the plague] shall be buried in any shirt, shift, sheet, or shroud, or anything whatsoever made or mingled with flax, hemp, silk, hair, gold, or silver, or any material or thing, other than what is made of sheep's wool. Act of 1648, repealed in 1814)
    - Untitled (Century Plant), 1998; 151253 (Box 19, Object ID: 200.2.0022)
      Medium: sepia-toned prints, frames
      Dimensions: 21" x 14.5"
      Description: Two photos of two different century plants in bloom. The century plant is said to blossom once every hundred years. The piece consists of two framed prints.
    - Untitled [doubleseat chair], 1998; 220.2.0027; 151258; 1 item one chair (Box 54, Object 220.2.0027)
      Medium: polyurethane, steel
      Dimensions: 32" x 33" x 24"
    - Untitled [cradle chair], 1998; 220.2.0028; 151259; 1 item one chair (Box 55, Object 220.2.0028)
      Dimensions: 31" x 25" x 24"
    - Untitled (eye frame), 1998; 151260 (Box 56, Object ID: 220.2.0029)
      Medium: prescription eyeglass, custom frame, glass shelf
      Dimensions: shelf: 2" x 9" x 10"
      Description: Installed at eye level. The eyeglass prescription matched Blanchon's own failing eyesight and eventual blindness in one eye, caused by symptoms related to HIV.
    - Untitled (Mies van der Rohe's Farnsworth House, Plano, Illinois on February 24, 1998, 2:46pm), cuid6056; 1 item one photograph (Item MSS.220.cuid6056)
    - Wave (0-9), 1996; 151250 (Box 23, Object ID: 220.2.0019)
      Medium: c-prints, ed. three
      Description: From an attempt to photograph two identical waves. Piece consists of 10 separate prints.
  - Subseries B: Collaborative Artwork, 151586
    Series I: Subseries B: Collaborative Artwork, contains artworks done by Blanchon in collaboration with other artists.
    - Cruising New York, Promotional Copy, 1993; 151587 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Medium: newsprint pages bound
      Dimensions: 8.5" x 11"
      Description: Promotional Copy (1993) is an artist publication with entries from many different contributors. Robert Blanchon's advertisement for Cruising New York appears in a 1993 issue of Promotional Copy on page 94.
    - Gilbert and George, 1994; 151588 (Folder 2 Left)
      Medium: three gelatin silver prints
      Dimensions: 42.5" x 32.5"
      Description: Photographs taken from original performance with Mary Ellen Carroll at Wigstock, 1994. Photograph also produced as a postcard multiple, edition unknown.
    - Stamp: Bed-in for Peace With-in, 1997; 151589 (Box 9)
      Medium: wood and rubber stamp
      Dimensions:
      Description: Bed-in for Peace With-in was conceived for an exhibition for Popular Mechanics Gallery in the Premiere Hollywood Hotel. With collaborator Kelly Marie Martin, Blanchon decorated the room in white and lay in a bed covered with self-help books. Fales holds the stamp produced in connection with the performance. Stamp transfers the following message: Bed-in for Peace With-in, Robert Blanchon + Kelly Marie Martin:
      drove from Paris to Amsterdam Hilton talking in our bed for a week... the newspaper said what're doing in bed... I said we're only trying to get some Peace - John Lennon 3.24.69
      drove from Koreatown to Hollywood Premiere talking in bed for a little time no one asked what're doing in bed...said we're only tring to get some Piece of Mind - Robert Blanchon + Kelly Marie Martin 8.11.97
    - Smackwater, 1998; 151590 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Medium: photograph
      Dimensions: 4" x 6"
      Description: Piece consists of a photo from the original performance entitled Smackwater, conceptualized by Robert Blanchon and performed by Mary Ellen Carroll. During the performance lyrics to Carole King's "Smack Water Jack", written in what Blanchon claimed was crystal meth affixed to vellum and mounted to a gallery wall, were scraped off by Mary Ellen Carroll with a razor blade. She then deposited the powder in a drug baggy and cut out the place where the text had been. Folder 16 in Box 4 contains a photocopy of the original photograph of the event.
  - Subseries C: Source Materials, 161918
    This subseries consists primarily of source materials for Blanchon's work, such as sketchbooks and test prints. Other materials included may not relate directly to realized artworks.
    - Blanchon Sketchbook, 161945 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Loose materials found in sketchbook, 161946 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Visual Materials, 161947 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Paint-and-Feather Assemblage, undated; 164979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Oversize Visual Source Material, undated; 164962 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Untitled [swimming pool], c. 1998; 151262 (Folder 5)
      Medium: cibachrome print
      Dimensions: 20" x 24"
      Description: Print was labeled "test print".
    - Untitled [desert], c. 1998; 151263 (Folder 5)
      Medium: c-print
    - Untitled [windshield], c. 1998; 151266 (Folder 5)
      Dimensions: 19.75" x 23.75"
    - Untitled [ducks], c. 1998; 151267 (Folder 5)
    - Untitled [There is beauty], c. 1998; 151268 (Folder 5)
      Dimensions: 20" x 23.75"
    - Untitled [rainy], c. 1998; 151269 (Folder 5)
      Dimensions: 30" x 40"
    - Untitled [garden], c. 1998; 151270 (Folder 5)
      Dimensions: 20" x 30"
    - Untitled [gum stain], 1995; 154088 (Folder 5)
      Medium: black and white photograph
      Dimensions: 23" x 30"
    - Untitled [envelopes], c. 1994; 156916 (Folder 5)
    - Untitled [Washington monument], undated (Folder 4 Right)
    - Photos, Posters, 161948 (Folder 6)
      Millie Wilson poster
      2 artworks by unidentified artists
    - Photograph of Blanchon's apartment in Silverlake, LA, 162004 (Box 57)
      Written on original container: "Robert's apartment in Silverlake" and "Honda parked in front of apartment bldg."
    - Production material for Untitled (aroma/1981), undated; 277395 (Folder 1 Left)
    - Bus Shelter Poster (Red), 1991; 162001 (Box 57)
      Dimensions: 48" x 70"
      Description: Poster by Mark Niblock-Smith. Lithograph. Funded by Los Angeles Cultural Affairs Department.
  - Subseries D: Publicity, Notes, etc., 162072
    Series I: Subseries D contains publicity materials (such as catalogs and postcards) for both Blanchon's work and the work of others, magazines and journals, and Blanchon's notes and source materials for projects.
    - Art / Literary Journals, Undated, 1995, 1998; 162840 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Catalogs, Undated, 1992, 1996; 162841 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Chopped Up in Silver Lake by Lucien Patrick, Notebook, Undated; 156002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Blank notebook with fake book cover. Blanchon made notes on the first couple of pages.
    - The Estate of Robert Blanchon Ephemera: Mail Art, Papers, Public Works, 1989-1999; 162842 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Exhibition Postcards (Blanchon), 1994, 1998; 162843 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Lalalalalalala...(Catalog), 1997; 162844 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Let's Just Kiss + Say Goodbye - EDL Lists + Disks, 1995; 162845 (Box 1, Folder 12, Box Shared Fales 016)
    - Let's Just Kiss + Say Goodbye - Notes, 1995; 162846 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Let's Just Kiss + Say Goodbye - Programs and Promotional Materials, 1995; 162847 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Let's Just Kiss + Say Goodbye - Programs and Promotional Materials, 1995; 162848 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Let's Just Kiss + Say Goodbye - Resources, 1995; 162849 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Let's Just Kiss + Say Goodbye - Script, 1995; 162850; This folder contains a floppy disk. (Box 1, Folder 17, Box Shared Fales 016)
    - Magazines and Catalogs, 1991-2000; 162851 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - [Never Realized] By Robert Blanchon, 1996; 162852 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Notes, Clippings, Etc., Undated; 162853 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Postcards and Announcements, 1990-2001; 162854 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Untitled (Left S/M Top - Right S/M Bottom), 1994; 163025 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Whitewalls Number 26, 1990; 162855 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Whitewalls Number 33 / 34, 1994; 162856 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Whitewalls Number 35, 1994; 162857 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Series II: Correspondence and Notes, 144251
  Series II: Notes and Correspondence contains letters related to Blanchon's teaching, art production and exhibitions, and personal life. The collection includes both letters received by Blancon, and copies he made of letters he sent to others. Notes appear in this series when they were already interfiled with correspondence.
  Some of the letters were damaged by paint; these have been photocopied, and access to the originals is restricted.
  - Correspondence, Undated; 157402 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1996; 157403 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1997; 157404 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1998; 157407 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1999; 157408 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (Damaged Originals) - RESTRICTED, 1997-1998; 157409 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Etc: Mary Ellen Carroll, 1994-1998, Undated; 157410 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Etc: Mary Ellen Carroll, Undated; 163034 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Marc Foxx, 1997-1998; 163035 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence + Notes For Uncompleted Works, 1997-1998; 163037 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence With Students, 1998; 163038 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Let's Just Kiss And Say Goodbye Correspondence, 1994-1995; 163039 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Whitewalls - A Wretch Like Me - Correspondence, 1994; 163044 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Series III: Teaching, 163048
  - Course Materials - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998; 163049 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Course Reader - Don't Smoke in Bed: The Graduate Critique as a Safe Space, Copy 1 (Folder 1 of 2), Fall 1996; 163051 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Course Reader - Don't Smoke in Bed: The Graduate Critique as a Safe Space, Copy 1 (Folder 2 of 2), Fall 1996; 163052 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Course Reader - Don't Smoke in Bed: The Graduate Critique as a Safe Space, Copy 2 (Folder 1 of 2), Fall 1996; 163053 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Course Reader - Don't Smoke in Bed: The Graduate Critique as a Safe Space, Copy 2 (Folder 2 of 2), Fall 1996; 163054 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Issues in Contemporary Art: Syllabus + Handouts, Fall 1995; 163055 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Issues in Contemporary Art: Syllabus + Final Exam, Winter 1996; 163056 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Course Reader - Issues in Contemporary Art 1980-Present, Spring 1996; 163058 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Course Reader - Issues in Contemporary Art, Marked-Up Copy 1 (Folder 1 of 2), Fall 1996; 163060 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Course Reader - Issues in Contemporary Art [Modernism], Marked-Up Copy 1 (Folder 2 of 2), Fall 1996; 163061 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Course Reader - Issues in Contemporary Art, Copy 2, Fall 1996; 163062 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Course Reader - Issues in Contemporary Art, Copy 3, Spring 1997; 163063 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Course Reader - Issues in Contemporary Art, Copy 4 + Related Papers, Spring 1997; 163064 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Course Reader - Reading Position for Second Degree Burn, Copy 1 of 2 (Folder 1 of 2), Winter 1997; 163065 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Course Reader - Reading Positions for Second Degree Burn (Issues in Contemporary Art: 1970s) (Folder 2 of 2), Winter 1997; 163066 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Course Reader - Reading Position for Second Degree Burn (Issues in Contemporary Art: 1970s), Copy 2 of 2, Winter 1997; 163067 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Course Reader - More Than 15 Minutes of Fame: The Graduate Critique as Learning Experience, Winter 1996; 163068 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Course Reader - Road Kill (or a Dinner Supplement), Copy 1 of 2, Spring 1997; 163069 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Course Reader - Road Kill (or a Dinner Supplement) + Related Papers, Copy 2 of 2, Spring 1997; 163070 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Course Reader - Ways of Dwelling + Related Papers, Fall 1997; 163071 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Course Reader - Yesterday's Kill: Fresh Blood Graduate Seminar, Winter 1997; 163072 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Course Reader - You Make Me Feel Mighty Reel (Folder 1 of 3), Winter/Spring 1998; 163073 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Course Reader - You Make Me Feel Mighty Reel + Related Papers (Folder 2 of 3), Winter/Spring 1998; 163074 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Course Reader - You Make Me Feel Mightly Reel [Restricted Content] (Folder 3 of 3), Winter/Spring 1998; 163075 (Box 3, Folder 9, Box Shared Fales 016)
    This folder includes restricted content in the form of floppy disks. Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Student Work - You Make Me Feel Mighty Reel, Art Institute of Chicago [Restricted Content], Spring 1999; 163076 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Series IV: Photography, 144253
  Series IV: Photography contains source photography for artworks, negative film, glass slides, contact sheets, artist test proofs, slides of artwork, and framed photographs of friends and family. Slides of artwork exist both in 8.5 x 11" photo sleeves, and in three archival slide box systems assumed to have been arranged by Blanchon. The slides in the slide boxes generally duplicate the slides that have been arranged into sleeves; access to the slide boxes is by approval only, and researchers should use the sleeved slides for viewing.
  One group of photographs has been processed within Series VII: Objects - see Object ID: 220.2.0055 "Box of family photographs".
  - Photographic Prints 8x10, Undated; 157470 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Photographic Prints 3x5 - 6x8, Undated; 163077 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Contact Sheets, undated; 157472 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Transparencies, Undated; 157473 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Transparencies in medium and large formats.
  - Negative Film, undated; 161886 (Box 14)
    35mm negative film strips arranged into labelled, tabbed archival film folders in small box. Arrangement and labels appear to be Blanchon's. Access is by permission only.
  - Negative Film, undated; 161887 (Box 15)
  - "Slide Box no. 1 (1985-1989)", 161871 (Box 10)
    Contains slides arranged into tabbed archival boxes by subject. Arrangement appears to be Blanchon's. Slides duplicate those found in slide sleeves (Box 13). Access by permission only.
  - "Slide Box no. 2 (1990-1997)", 161872 (Box 11)
    Contains slides arranged into tabbed archival boxes by subject. Arrangement appears to be Blanchon's. Slides duplicate those found in slide sleeves (box 13). Access by permission only.
  - "Slide Box no. 3 (1994-1998 and installation views)", 161873 (Box 12)
  - Slides of artworks, 1985-1998; 161867 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Ten 8.5 x 11" slide sleeves of slides of Blanchon's artworks.
  - Slides of artworks, 1989-1996; 161868 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Slides of artworks, 1985-1998; 161869 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Slides of artworks, 1992-1998; 161870 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Six 8.5 x 11" slide sleeves of slides of Blanchon's artworks.
- Series V: Media, 144254
  Series V: Media contains Robert Blanchon's film works in multiple formats including VHS, Digital Betacam, and DVD. Series also contains cassette tapes, compact discs, and records.
  - Subseries A: Video - Access Copies, 160031
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - let's just kiss + say goodbye, 1995; ID: 220.0042; 192038 (Case 220.0042)
      Format: DVD
      Color, B&W, Sound
      Duration: 00:09:00
      Source: BetacamSP ID# 220.0018
      Note: This dvd has an introductory Fales logo, title card, and is "looped" for exhibition purposes.
  - Subseries B: Video - Originals, 160273
    - AIDS 2006 Film Festival: Overdue Conversation, Cruiser, United in Anger, Motet for Zackie & Pils Slip, Smalltown Boys, Black (N. Adj.), August 11, 2006; ID: 220.0027; 160428 (Box 6, Media ID: 220.0027)
      Format: BetacamSP
      Duration: [unknown]
    - Blanchon Tape 1: Fade- from VHS, undated; ID: 220.0001; 160033 (Box 6, Media ID: 220.0001)
      Duration: 00:30:00
    - Blanchon Tape 2: Fade- from VHS, undated; ID: 220.0002; 160034 (Box 6, Media ID: 220.0002)
    - Blanchon Tape 3: Homicide 306 (Digital from Avid of Scene 16), September 4, 1994; ID: 220.0003; 160035 (Box 6, Media ID: 220.0003)
    - Blanchon Tape 4: Raw, undated; ID: 220.0004; 160036 (Box 6, Media ID: 220.0004)